ILGWU Southeast Region Records 5780/058
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Feature Manufacturing Company., 1953-1958 (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Feature Manufacturing Company. Payroll Sheets., 1953-1954 (Box 23, Folder 2)
- Fashion Frocks, Inc., 1945-1952 (Box 23, Folder 3)
- Federal Corset Company., 1953-1965 (Box 23, Folder 4)
- Federal of Union Representatives., 1960-1961 (Box 23, Folder 5)
- Federation of Union Representatives., 1961-1962 (Box 23, Folder 6)
- Financial Reports., 1949-1954 (Box 24, Folder 1)
- Flagg-Utica Corporation., 1965 (Box 24, Folder 2)
- Flagg-Utica Corporation., 1960-1965 (Box 24, Folder 3)
- Flagg-Utica Corporation., 1957-1959 (Box 24, Folder 4)
- Flagg-Utica Corporation., 1955-1958 (Box 24, Folder 5)
- Flagg-Utica Corporation., 1955-1956 (Box 24, Folder 6)
- Flagg-Utica Corporation., 1944-1954 (Box 24, Folder 7)
- Correspondence. Staff Members., 1951-1954 (Box 25, Folder 1)
- Four Freedoms Hotels., 1961 (Box 25, Folder 2)
- Correspondence. G., 1959-1969 (Box 25, Folder 3)
- Correspondence. G., 1960-1968 (Box 25, Folder 4)
- G.C. Lingerie Corporation., 1965-1966 (Box 25, Folder 5)
- G.C. Lingerie Corporation., 1967-1968 (Box 25, Folder 6)
- G.C. Lingerie Corporation., 1968-1969 (Box 25, Folder 7)
- G.C. Lingerie Corporation. Agreement with ILGWU., 1966-1967 (Box 26, Folder 1)
- G.C. Lingerie Corporation., 1965 (Box 26, Folder 2)
- G.C. Lingerie. Cases., 1962-1963 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  Scope and Contents
  Case No. 10-CA-5060, 5116, 5215, 5329, 5379
- G.C. Lingerie Corporation. Cases., 1965 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  Case No. 10-RC-6450 & 10-CA-6417
- G.C. Lingerie Corporation. Cases., 1966 (Box 26, Folder 5)
- G.C. Lingerie Corporation. Affidavits., 1965-1966 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  R&C Cases
- G.C. Lingerie Corporation. Cases., 1963-1964 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  Case No. 10-RC-5869, 10-RM-369, 10-CA-5564
- G.C. Lingerie Corporation. Affidavits., 1962 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  Case No. 10-CA-5060
- Garland Knitting Mills. Cases. General., 1966-1968 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  Case No. 1-RM-570, 1-RC-8878, 1-CA-5400, 5622
- Garland Knitting Mills. Cases. Factual Material., 1960-1966 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  Case No. 1-RM-570, 1-RC-8878, 1-CA- 5400,5622
- Garland Knitting Mills. CA and RC Cases. Warrenton & Beaufort. [folder 1 of 4], 1966 (Box 27, Folder 3)
- Garland Knitting Mills. CA and RC Cases. Warrenton & Beaufort. [folder 2 of 4], 1960-1966 (Box 27, Folder 4)
- Garland Knitting Mills. CA and RC Cases. Warrenton & Beaufort. [folder 3 of 4], 1967-1968 (Box 27, Folder 5)
- Garland Knitting Mills. CA and RC Cases. Warrenton & Beaufort. [folder 4 of 4], 1967-1969 (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Garland Knitting Mills. Beaufort. CA and RC Cases. Statements., 1966 (Box 28, Folder 2)
- Garland Knitting Mills. Warrenton. CA and RC Cases. Statements., 1966 (Box 28, Folder 3)
- Garland Knitting Mills. Trial Brief File., 1966 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  Case No. 10-CA-6720 et al., 11-CA-3067 et al.
- Garland Knitting Mills. ULP Evidence File., 1966 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  10-CA-6720 et al., 11-CA-3067 et al.
- Garland Knitting Mills. Exceptions to TXD., 1967 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  Case 11-CA-3067 et al.
- Garland Knitting Mills. Brief to TX., 1966 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  Case No. 11-CA-3067 et al.
- Garland Knitting Mills. Beaufort. Trial Exhibits. [folder 1 of 2], 1966 (Box 29, Folder 2)
- Garland Knitting Mills. Beaufort. Trial Exhibits. [folder 2 of 2], 1967 (Box 29, Folder 3)
- Garland Knitting Mills. Brief to TX., 1967 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  Case No. 10-CA-6720 & 6752
- General Executive Board., 1947-1961 (Box 29, Folder 5)
- Georgia Department of Labor., 1950-1953 (Box 29, Folder 6)
- Glendale Manufacturing Company., 1955 (Box 30, Folder 1)
- Glendale Manufacturing Company. Correspondence and Clippings., 1955 (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Glendale Manufacturing Company., 1956-1958 (Box 30, Folder 3)
- Glendale Manufacturing Company., 1958-1964 (Box 30, Folder 4)
- Glendale Manufacturing Company. Bainbridge and Panama City., 1963-1965 (Box 30, Folder 5)
- Greene Manufacturing Company and Jonathan Logan, Inc., 1964 (Box 30, Folder 6)
- Greene Manufacturing Company., 1965-1966 (Box 30, Folder 7)
- Greene Manufacturing Company., 1966-1969 (Box 30, Folder 8)
- Greensboro Strike Expenses., 1955 (Box 31, Folder 1)
- Greensboro Strike Expenses., 1954 (Box 31, Folder 2)
- Greensboro Strike. Misc., 1953-1954 (Box 31, Folder 3)
- Greensboro Strike. Clippings., 1954 (Box 31, Folder 4)
- "H" Correspondence. Misc., 1967-1969 (Box 31, Folder 5)
- "H" Correspondence. Misc., 1957-1961 (Box 31, Folder 6)
- Haleyville Textile Mill., 1956-1958 (Box 31, Folder 7)
- Haleyville Textile Mill. Clippings., 1956-1958 (Box 31, Folder 8)
- Haleyville Textile Mill Company., 1955-1957 (Box 32, Folder 1)
- Hallie Lee, Inc., 1958 (Box 32, Folder 2)
- Handler, Jack G. Correspondence., 1966-1969 (Box 32, Folder 3)
- Hartsville Manufacturing Company., 1965-1969 (Box 32, Folder 4)
- Hartsville Manufacturing Company., 1963-1965 (Box 32, Folder 5)
- Hartsville Manufacturing Company., 1958-1963 (Box 32, Folder 6)
- Hartsville Manufacturing Company., 1954-1957 (Box 32, Folder 7)
- Hartsville Manufacturing Company., 1952-1954 (Box 32, Folder 8)
- Hartsville Manufacturing Company., 1948-1953 (Box 32, Folder 9)
- Haskel, Hanna. Correspondence., 1957-1960 (Box 33, Folder 1)
- Hawkinsville Manufacturing Company, Inc., 1959-1963 (Box 33, Folder 2)
- Southeastern Region Health and Welfare Fund., 1966-1969 (Box 33, Folder 3)
- Southeastern Region Health and Welfare Fund., 1966-1967 (Box 33, Folder 4)
- Southeastern Region Health and Welfare Fund., 1964-1965 (Box 33, Folder 5)
- Southeastern Region Health and Welfare Fund., 1956-1965 (Box 33, Folder 6)
- Southeastern Region Health and Welfare Fund. Correspondence., 1954-1955 (Box 33, Folder 7)
- Southeastern Region Health and Welfare Fund. Misc., 1953-1954 (Box 33, Folder 8)
- Southeastern Region Health and Welfare Fund., 1945-1951 (Box 33, Folder 9)
- Hialeah Knitting Mills, Inc., 1968-1970 (Box 34, Folder 1)
- Hialeah Knitting Mills, Inc., 1964-1967 (Box 34, Folder 2)
- Hobco Manufacturing Company., 1965 (Box 34, Folder 3)
- Hobco Manufacturing Company. Brief File No.1., 1965 (Box 34, Folder 4)
- Hobco Manufacturing Company. Brief File No.2., 1966-1967 (Box 34, Folder 5)
- Hobco Manufacturing Company. Trial Examiner's Decision., 1965-1966 (Box 34, Folder 6)
- Hobco Manufacturing Company. Trial File., 1966 (Box 34, Folder 7)
- Hobco Manufacturing Company. Affidavits., 1965 (Box 35, Folder 1)
- Hobco Manufacturing Company. Campaign Literature., 1965 (Box 35, Folder 2)
- Hobco Manufacturing Company. Case 10-CA-6986., 1967 (Box 35, Folder 3)
- Hobco Manufacturing Company. General Commencing. [folder 1 of 2], 1967-1968 (Box 35, Folder 4)
- Hobco Manufacturing Company. General Commencing. [folder 2 of 2], 1967-1968 (Box 35, Folder 5)
- Hobco Manufacturing Company. Case 10-RC-6449. [folder 1 of 2], 1966-1968 (Box 35, Folder 6)
- Hobco Manufacturing Company. Case 10-RC-6449. [folder 2 of 2], 1966-1968 (Box 35, Folder 7)
- Holeproof Hosiery Company., 1954-1955 (Box 36, Folder 1)
- Holeproof Hosiery Company., 1952-1953 (Box 36, Folder 2)
- Holeproof Hosiery Company. Luxite Division., 1951-1952 (Box 36, Folder 3)
- Holeproof Hosiery Company. Luxite Division., 1947-1950 (Box 36, Folder 4)
- Hollywood Vassarette. Division of Musingwear, Inc., 1966-1969 (Box 36, Folder 5)
- Homesteads Knitting Mills, Inc., 1958-1959 (Box 36, Folder 6)
- Jules Honig, Inc., 1953-1954 (Box 36, Folder 7)
- ILGWU Training Institute., 1957-1965 (Box 37, Folder 1)
- ILGWU Training Institute., 1955-1956 (Box 37, Folder 2)
- ILGWU Training Institute., 1951-1954 (Box 37, Folder 3)
- Industrial Union Department., 1961-1962 (Box 37, Folder 4)
- International Outerwear, Inc., 1968-1970 (Box 37, Folder 5)
- International Outerwear, Inc., 1965-1966 (Box 37, Folder 6)
- "J" Correspondence. Misc., 1960-1969 (Box 37, Folder 7)
- Jackson Apparel Manufacturing Company., 1962-1968 (Box 37, Folder 8)
- Jackson Apparel Manufacturing Company., 1957-1959 (Box 37, Folder 9)
- Jackson Garment Company, Inc., 1956 (Box 38, Folder 1)
- Jackson Garment Company, Inc., 1954-1955 (Box 38, Folder 2)
- Jackson Garment Company, Inc., 1954-1955 (Box 38, Folder 3)
- Jackson Garment Company, Inc., 1950-1954 (Box 38, Folder 4)
- Jacobs, Joseph. Correspondence., 1946-1951 (Box 38, Folder 5)
- Jasper Brassiere Company., 1955-1965 (Box 38, Folder 6)
- Jay Apparel Company., 1964-1969 (Box 38, Folder 7)
- Jay Apparel Company., 1953-1959 (Box 38, Folder 8)
- Jewish Labor Committee., 1957-1961 (Box 39, Folder 1)
- Jo-Log Sportswear, Inc., 1959-1968 (Box 39, Folder 2)
- Jonathan Logan, Inc., 1968-1969 (Box 39, Folder 3)
- Jonathan Logan, Inc., 1956-1978 (Box 39, Folder 4)
- Jonathan Logan, Inc. Master Agreement., 1964-1969 (Box 39, Folder 5)
- Jonathan Logan, Inc. Butte Knitting Mills., 1968-1969 (Box 39, Folder 6)
- Jonathan Logan, Inc. Kingston Dresses, Inc., 1964-1969 (Box 39, Folder 7)
- Jonathan Logan, Inc. Butte Knitting Mills. Negotiations., 1966-1968 (Box 40, Folder 1)
- Jonathan Logan, Inc. Butte Knitting Mills., 1969 (Box 40, Folder 2)
- Jonathan Logan, Inc. Andrew and Butte Knitting Mills Agreement, 1966-1968 (Box 40, Folder 3)
- Jonathan Logan, Inc. Kingston Dresses and Butte Knitting Mills Agreement., 1960-1969 (Box 40, Folder 4)
- Jonathan Logan, Inc. Butte Knitting Mills "Contact"., 1967-1972 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  Vol. III No. 5- Vol. IIX No.3
- Jonathan Logan, Inc. Debra Knit., 1967-1969 (Box 40, Folder 6)
- Jonathan Logan, Inc. Arbitration of Second Wildcat and Discharges., 1967-1968 (Box 40, Folder 7)
- Jonathan Logan, Inc. Butte Knitting Mills. Diverse Arbitrations., 1968 (Box 40, Folder 8)
- Judy Bond, Inc. Brewton Fashions, Inc., 1964-1969 (Box 41, Folder 1)
- Judy Bond, Inc. Misc., 1964-1965 (Box 41, Folder 2)
- Judy Bond, Inc. Brewton Fashions, Inc., 1964 (Box 41, Folder 3)
- Judy Bond, Inc. Brewton Fashions, Inc., 1963-1964 (Box 41, Folder 4)
- Judy Bond, Inc. Misc., 1962 (Box 41, Folder 5)
- Judy Bond, Inc. Brewton Fashions, Inc. Clippings., 1962-1965 (Box 41, Folder 6)
- Judy Bond, Inc. Brewton Fashions, Inc., 1965-1958 (Box 41, Folder 7)
- Judy Bond, Inc., 1968-1969 (Box 42, Folder 1)
- "Justice". Correspondence., 1961-1967 (Box 42, Folder 2)
- "Justice". Misc., 1957-1960 (Box 42, Folder 3)
- "K" Correspondence. Misc., 1960-1969 (Box 42, Folder 4)
- "K" Correspondence. Misc., 1957-1960 (Box 42, Folder 5)
- Kehrer, E.T. Correspondence., 1955-1969 (Box 42, Folder 6)
- Kelwood. Misc., 1966 (Box 42, Folder 7)
- Kemp, Maida Springer. Correspondence., 1966-1968 (Box 42, Folder 8)
- Ken-Lee, Inc., 1954-1964 (Box 43, Folder 1)
- Ken-Lee, Inc., 1960-1963 (Box 43, Folder 2)
- Ken-Lee, Inc. Refusal to Bargain., 1962-1964 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  Case 10-CA-4905
- Ken-Lee, Inc. Concerted Activities., 1960 (Box 43, Folder 4)
- Kentmore Company of NY., 1966-1967 (Box 43, Folder 5)
- Kingsboro, Mills, Inc., 1957 (Box 43, Folder 6)
- Kingston Dresses, Inc., 1966-1968 (Box 43, Folder 7)
- Kirtzman, Nicholas. Correspondence., 1960 (Box 43, Folder 8)
- Kleetblatt, Melvin. Correspondence., 1957-1962 (Box 43, Folder 9)
- Kramer, Edward Correspondence., 1957-1962 (Box 43, Folder 10)
- "L" Correspondence., 1957-1961 (Box 44, Folder 1)
- "L" Correspondence., 1961-1970 (Box 44, Folder 2)
- Labor, U.S. Department of., 1941-1960 (Box 44, Folder 3)
- Lamar Manufacturing Company., 1956 (Box 44, Folder 4)
- Laura Industries, Inc. [folder 1 of 2], 1967-1968 (Box 44, Folder 5)
- Laura Industries, Inc. [folder 2 of 2], 1967-1968 (Box 44, Folder 6)
- Laura Industries, Inc. Cases., 1968 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  Case No. 15-RC-3889
- Lawrence Corporation. "CA" Case. [folder 1 of 2], 1968 (Box 44, Folder 8)
- Lawrence Corporation. "CA" Case. [folder 2 of 2], 1968 (Box 44, Folder 9)
- Lawrence Corporation. "RC" Case., 1965-1968 (Box 44, Folder 10)
- Leemar Corporation., 1967-1969 (Box 45, Folder 1)
- Leemar Corporation., 1966-1969 (Box 45, Folder 2)
- Leemar Corporation. Agreement., 1964-1966 (Box 45, Folder 3)
- Leemar Corporation. Negotiations., 1967 (Box 45, Folder 4)
- Legal Department, ILGWU., 1966-1969 (Box 45, Folder 5)
- Legal Department, ILGWU., 1957-1962 (Box 45, Folder 6)
- Legal Department, ILGWU., 1954-1955 (Box 45, Folder 7)
- Legal Department, ILGWU., 1953-1954 (Box 45, Folder 8)
- Legal Department, ILGWU., 1951-1952 (Box 46, Folder 1)
- Legal Department, ILGWU., 1947-1951 (Box 46, Folder 2)
- Labor Statewide Conference, Nashville TN., 1967 (Box 46, Folder 3)
- Leslie Fay, Inc., 1966-1968 (Box 46, Folder 4)
- Levi Strauss and Company., 1964 (Box 46, Folder 5)
- Levi Strauss and Company. [folder 1 of 2], 1964-1965 (Box 46, Folder 6)
- Levi Strauss and Company. [folder 2 of 2], 1964-1965 (Box 46, Folder 7)
- Levi Strauss and Company vs. Chemical Workers Union., 1966-1967 (Box 46, Folder 8)
- Levi Strauss and Company. Case 10-RM-477., 1967 (Box 47, Folder 1)
- Levi Strauss and Company. Statements., 1966-1967 (Box 47, Folder 2)
- Levi Strauss and Company. Work Stoppage UC Cases., 1967 (Box 47, Folder 3)
- Levi Strauss and Company. Withdrawals., 1965 (Box 47, Folder 4)
- Levi Strauss and Company. Agreement., 1964 (Box 47, Folder 5)
- Levi Strauss and Company. Grievance Cases., 1965-1966 (Box 47, Folder 6)
- Levi Strauss and Company. General File. [folder 1 of 3], 1965 (Box 47, Folder 7)
- Levi Strauss and Company. General File. [folder 2 of 3], 1966 (Box 47, Folder 8)
- Levi Strauss and Company. General File. [folder 3 of 3], 1967-1968 (Box 47, Folder 9)
- Levi Strauss and Company. Injunctive Action., 1966-1968 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  Case No.1699- Levi Vs. Davis et al.
- Levi Strauss and Company. Misc., 1966 (Box 48, Folder 2)
- Levi Strauss and Company. Damage Action., 1966-1967 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  Case No. B-22767
- Levi Strauss and Company. Pre 1966 Grievance & Arbitration Cases., 1964-1965 (Box 48, Folder 4)
- Levi Strauss and Company. Blue Ridge Cases., 1964 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  No. 10-CA-5694, 10-CA-5707, 10-CA-6133, 10-CA-5683, 10-RC-5844
- Locals Correspondence. Misc., 1958-1966 (Box 48, Folder 6)
- Local 91. Correspondence., 1957-1962 (Box 48, Folder 7)
- Local 122. Correspondence., 1938-1950 (Box 49, Folder 1)
- Local 122, ILGWU., 1951-1953 (Box 49, Folder 2)
- Local 122, ILGWU., 1953-1954 (Box 49, Folder 3)
- Local 122, ILGWU., 1954-1955 (Box 49, Folder 4)
- Local 122, ILGWU., 1955-1962 (Box 49, Folder 5)
- Local 122, ILGWU., 1957-1959 (Box 49, Folder 6)
- Local 378, ILGWU., 1944-1955 (Box 49, Folder 7)
- Local 378, ILGWU., 1957 (Box 49, Folder 8)
- Locals, Misc., 1958-1966 (Box 49, Folder 9)
- Louis Levine and Sons., 1959-1960 (Box 49, Folder 10)
- Logan, Charles, H., 1950-1954 (Box 49, Folder 11)
- Lori-Ann of Miami, Inc. [folder 1 of 2], 1961-1962 (Box 50, Folder 1)
- Lori-Ann of Miami, Inc. [folder 2 of 2], 1961-1962 (Box 50, Folder 2)
- Lori-Ann of Miami, Inc., 1961 (Box 50, Folder 3)
- Lovestone, Jay. Correspondence., 1949 (Box 50, Folder 4)
- "M" Correspondence., 1955-1959 (Box 50, Folder 5)
- "M" Correspondence., 1960-1968 (Box 50, Folder 6)
- MaCoy, Ramelle. Correspondence., 1966-1969 (Box 50, Folder 7)
- Martin, John S. Correspondence., 1946 (Box 50, Folder 8)
- Maazol Manufacturing Corporation., 1967-1969 (Box 50, Folder 9)
- Management Engineering Department. Correspondence., 1942-1961 (Box 50, Folder 10)
- Marion Mills of Munsingwear, Inc., 1957-1958 (Box 51, Folder 1)
- Marion Mills of Munsingwear, Inc., 1958 (Box 51, Folder 2)
- Marlene Industries Corporation. "CA" and 10(j) Cases. [folder 1 of 7], 1965-1968 (Box 51, Folder 3)
- Marlene Industries Corporation. "CA" and 10(j) Cases. [folder 2 of 7], 1965-1968 (Box 51, Folder 4)
- Marlene Industries Corporation. "CA" and 10(j) Cases. [folder 3 of 7], 1965-1968 (Box 51, Folder 5)
- Marlene Industries Corporation. "CA" and 10(j) Cases. [folder 4 of 7], 1965-1968 (Box 51, Folder 6)
- Marlene Industries Corporation. "CA" Cases and 10(j) Cases. [folder 5 of 7], 1965-1968 (Box 52, Folder 1)
- Marlene Industries Corporation. "CA" Cases and 10(j) Cases. [folder 6 of 7], 1965-1968 (Box 52, Folder 2)
- Marlene Industries Corporation. "CA" Cases and 10(j) Cases. [folder 7 of 7], 1965-1968 (Box 52, Folder 3)
- Marlene Industries Corporation. Potential "CA" for Civil Case., 1968 (Box 52, Folder 4)
- Memorandums., 1957-1959 (Box 52, Folder 5)
- Memorandums., 1960-1969 (Box 52, Folder 6)
- Miami Joint Council., 1955-1959 (Box 53, Folder 1)
- Miami Joint Council., 1959-1960 (Box 53, Folder 2)
- Miami Joint Council. Miami Joint Council., 1960-1961 (Box 53, Folder 3)
- Miami Joint Council., 1961-1962 (Box 53, Folder 4)
- Miami Joint Council., 1965-1966 (Box 53, Folder 5)
- Morand, Martin J. Correspondence., 1966 (Box 53, Folder 6)
- Morand, Martin J. Correspondence., 1967 (Box 53, Folder 7)
- Morand, Martin J. and Harry Metz. Correspondence., 1968 (Box 53, Folder 8)
- Metz, Harry. Correspondence., 1969-1970 (Box 54, Folder 1)
- Miami, ILGWU., 1970 (Box 54, Folder 2)
- Miami. Staff Reports., 1967-1968 (Box 54, Folder 3)
- Miami. Staff Reports., 1967 (Box 54, Folder 4)
- Milwaukee Joint Board. Correspondence w/ John S. Martin and Harry P. Bovshow., 1950-1952 (Box 54, Folder 5)
- Minimum Wage Issues., 1966 (Box 54, Folder 6)
- Martin, John S. Correspondence, 1946-1953 (Box 54, Folder 7)
- Misc. Correspondence., 1953-1969 (Box 54, Folder 8)
- Miss Adventure, Inc., 1968 (Box 55, Folder 1)
- Miss Adventure, Inc., 1967-1968 (Box 55, Folder 2)
- Mississippi Labor Council., 1961-1962 (Box 55, Folder 3)
- Mitchell, J.W., 1961 (Box 55, Folder 4)
- Mobile Health Center., 1957 (Box 55, Folder 5)
- Mobile Health Units., 1958-1960 (Box 55, Folder 6)
- Mobile Health Units., 1961-1968 (Box 55, Folder 7)
- Moulton Shirt Corporation. [folder 1 of 2], 1966-1967 (Box 55, Folder 8)
  Case No. 10-CA-6778
- Moulton Shirt Corporation. [folder 2 of 2], 1967 (Box 55, Folder 9)
- Moulton Shirt Corporation., 1967-1968 (Box 55, Folder 10)
  Case No. 10-RC-7100
- Moulton Shirt Corporation., 1967 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  Case No. 10-CA-6962
- Moulton Manufacturing Company., 1965-1966 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  Case No. 10-CA-5648
- Moulton Manufacturing Company., 1963-1967 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  Case No. 10-RC-5579
- Mountain Top, Inc., 1958 (Box 56, Folder 4)
- Movie Star, Inc., 1957-1962 (Box 56, Folder 5)
- Movie Star, Inc., 1957-1958 (Box 56, Folder 6)
- Movie Star, Inc., 1949-1955 (Box 56, Folder 7)
- Movie Star, Inc. Health and Welfare Fund., 1959-1960 (Box 56, Folder 8)
- Movie Star, Inc., 1958-1960 (Box 56, Folder 9)
- Movie Star, Inc., 1956 (Box 56, Folder 10)
- Movie Star, Inc., 1956-1958 (Box 57, Folder 1)
- Movie Star, Inc. Health and Welfare Fund., 1956-1957 (Box 57, Folder 2)
- Movie Star, Inc. Health and Welfare Fund., 1958-1960 (Box 57, Folder 3)
- Movie Star of Poplarville, Inc. Health and Welfare Fund., 1954-1955 (Box 57, Folder 4)
- Movie Star of Poplarville, Inc. Health and Welfare Fund., 1955 (Box 57, Folder 5)
- Movie Star of Poplarville, Inc. Payroll., 1955-1956 (Box 57, Folder 6)
- Movie Star of Poplarville, Inc. Payroll., 1956-1957 (Box 57, Folder 7)
- Movie Star of Poplarville, Inc. Misc., 1956 (Box 57, Folder 8)
- Movie Star of Poplarville, Inc. Payroll., 1957 (Box 58, Folder 1)
- Movie Star of Poplarville, Inc. Health and Welfare Fund. Wage Breakdowns., 1957 (Box 58, Folder 2)
- Movie Star of Poplarville, Inc. Health and Welfare Fund. Wage Breakdowns., 1959 (Box 58, Folder 3)
- Movie Star of Poplarville, Inc. Misc., 1958 (Box 58, Folder 4)
- Movie Star of Poplarville, Inc. Payroll., 1958 (Box 58, Folder 5)
- Movie Star, Inc., 1965-1966 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  Case No. 15-CA-2154
- Movie Star, Inc. v. NLRB, 1962 (Box 58, Folder 7)
- Movie Star, Inc., 1963-1964 (Box 58, Folder 8)
  Case No. 10-CA-2404
- Movie Star, Inc. Overtime Arbitration., 1962-1963 (Box 58, Folder 9)
- Movie Star, Inc. Piece Rates and Arbitration., 1963 (Box 59, Folder 1)
- Movie Star, Inc., 1964 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  Case No. 15-CA-2154, 15-RM-166
- Movie Star, Inc., 1963-1964 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  Case. No. 10-RM-166, 15-CA-2154
- Mylcraft Manufacturing Company., 1967 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  11-CA-3357, 3377, 3431
- Mylcraft Manufacturing Company., 1967-1968 (Box 59, Folder 5)
  Case No. 11-CA-3357, 3377, 3431
- Mylcraft Manufacturing Company., 1968 (Box 59, Folder 6)
  Case No. 11-RM-144
- Mylcraft Manufacturing Company., 1966-1967 (Box 59, Folder 7)
  Case No. 11-RM-134
- Mylcraft Manufacturing Company, Inc. Contract Negotiations. [folder 1 of 3], 1967 (Box 60, Folder 1)
- Mylcraft Manufacturing Company, Inc. Contract Negotiations. [folder 2 of 3], 1967 (Box 60, Folder 2)
- Mylcraft Manufacturing Company, Inc. Contract Negotiations. [folder 3 of 3], 1967-1968 (Box 60, Folder 3)
- "N" Correspondence. Misc., 1954-1961 (Box 60, Folder 4)
- Hochman, Julius. Misc. Correspondence., 1946-1961 (Box 60, Folder 5)
- NAACP Correspondence. E.H. Kehrer and Herbert Hill., 1954 (Box 60, Folder 6)
- Northeast Department. Correspondence., 1946-1969 (Box 60, Folder 7)
- Office Employees International Union. Correspondence., 1959-1969 (Box 60, Folder 8)
- Oakley Fashions, Inc., 1967-1969 (Box 60, Folder 9)
- Oakley Fashions, Inc., 1967 (Box 60, Folder 10)
- Oakley Fashions, Inc., 1966-1968 (Box 61, Folder 1)
- Oakley Fashions, Inc. Jackson, TN., 1962-1966 (Box 61, Folder 2)
- Oneita Knitting Mills, Inc., 1952-1953 (Box 61, Folder 3)
- Oneita Knitting Mills, Inc., 1954-1956 (Box 61, Folder 4)
- Oneita Knitting Mills, Inc. Correspondence., 1957-1962 (Box 61, Folder 5)
- Oneita Knitting Mills, Inc., 1965-1968 (Box 61, Folder 6)
- Onslow Garment Industries. Correspondence., 1967 (Box 61, Folder 7)
- Orangeburg Garment Company, Inc., 1949-1952 (Box 61, Folder 8)
- Pearce, Ed. Esq. Correspondence., 1954 (Box 61, Folder 9)
- Philadelphia Joint Board. Sam Otto Correspondence., 1937-1962 (Box 62, Folder 1)
- "P" Correspondence., 1948-1959 (Box 62, Folder 2)
- Palmetto Manufacturing Company, Inc. and ILGWU Local 122. [folder 1 of 6], 1965 (Box 62, Folder 3)
- Palmetto Manufacturing Company, Inc. and ILGWU Local 122. [folder 2 of 6], 1965 (Box 62, Folder 4)
- Palmetto Manufacturing Company, Inc. and ILGWU Local 122. [folder 3 of 6], 1965 (Box 62, Folder 5)
- Palmetto Manufacturing Company, Inc. and ILGWU Local 122. [folder 4 of 6], 1966 (Box 62, Folder 6)
- Palmetto Manufacturing Company, Inc. and ILGWU Local 122. [folder 5 of 6], 1966 (Box 62, Folder 7)
- Palmetto Manufacturing Company, Inc. and ILGWU Local 122. [folder 6 of 6], 1966 (Box 63, Folder 1)
- Palmetto Manufacturing Company, Inc. Court Actions., 1965 (Box 63, Folder 2)
- Palmetto Manufacturing Company, Inc. NLRB., 1965-1966 (Box 63, Folder 3)
- Palmetto Manufacturing Company, Inc. NLRB., 1965 (Box 63, Folder 4)
- Perlstein, Meyer. Correspondence., 1938-1955 (Box 63, Folder 5)
- Pettibelle, Inc., 1957 (Box 63, Folder 6)
- Pettibelle, Inc. Misc., 1957 (Box 63, Folder 7)
- Pioneer Manufacturing Company, Inc., 1956-1957 (Box 63, Folder 8)
- Pleasure Togs, Inc., 1952-1959 (Box 63, Folder 9)
- Plotkin, Abraham. Correspondence., 1946-1955 (Box 63, Folder 10)
- Political Department., 1948-1960 (Box 64, Folder 1)
- Political Department., 1960-1961 (Box 64, Folder 2)
- Political Department., 1961-1965 (Box 64, Folder 3)
- Politics. Campaign Committees., 1965-1966 (Box 64, Folder 4)
- Politics., 1966-1967 (Box 64, Folder 5)
- Political Department. Educational Trips., 1967-1969 (Box 64, Folder 6)
- Political Education Club., 1965-1968 (Box 64, Folder 7)
- Poole, Pearce and Hall., 1952-1955 (Box 64, Folder 8)
- Polly Prentiss, Inc., 1950 (Box 64, Folder 9)
- Politics. "With These Hands"., 1950-1954 (Box 64, Folder 10)
- Puritan Fashions Corporation., 1965-1970 (Box 65, Folder 1)
- Puritan Fashions Corporation., 1965-1970 (Box 65, Folder 1)
- Puritan Fashions Corporation. Agreement., 1964-1969 (Box 65, Folder 2)
- Puritan Fashions Corporation. Agreement., 1964-1969 (Box 65, Folder 2)
- Puritan Fashions Corporation. Agreement., 1966-1967 (Box 65, Folder 3)